http://www.keepandbeararms.com/about/privacy_policy.asp

EMAIL NEWS
Main Email List:
State Email Lists:
YOUR VOTE COUNTS
Do you support Michael Bloomberg's efforts to shred the Second Amendment?NoYes
» SEMPER FIrearms
» Colt Collectors Assoc.
KeepAndBearArms.com has created this privacy statement
in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to Privacy. The following discloses
our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.  We
are committed to providing improvements in the below policy if warranted.
By accessing or using the KeepAndBearArms.com web site,
you agree to the terms of the KeepAndBearArms.com Privacy Policy, as outlined
below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access
or use this site. KeepAndBearArms.com reserves the right to change its
Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your
use of this site will be subject to the most current version of
the Privacy Policy at the time of such use.
Collection of Personal Information
When you engage in certain activities on
this site, such as ordering products, downloading software, or
entering contests, KeepAndBearArms.com may ask you to provide certain
information about yourself by filling out and submitting an
online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in
these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities,
however, KeepAndBearArms.com may ask that you provide us personal
information, such as your first and last name, mailing address
(including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and
department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal
identifying information. When ordering products or services on
the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number.
Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask
you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary.
If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a
particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that
activity. In the process of administering our site, we maintain
and track usage through Web server logs. Web server logs provide
such information as what types of browsers are accessing our
site, what pages receive high traffic, and the times of day our
servers experience significant load. We use this information to
improve the content and navigation features of our site. It is
not used to personally identify you.
Your Personal Information
KeepAndBearArms.com collects your information in order
to record and support your participation in the activities you
select. The information that you provide is also used as part of
our effort to keep you informed about special offers and other
products and services of KeepAndBearArms.com and selected third parties.
Share Your Personal Information
We will not sell, rent or lease to others
telephone numbers or e-mail addresses. We will share the
personal data you provide only with other KeepAndBearArms.com entities and/or
business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses
described above, except as provided below (see Consent).
Consent
KeepAndBearArms.com will use and share the personally
identifiable information you provided to us in ways related to
those described above. We reserve the right to disclose any and
all pertinent customer information to law enforcement or other
government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe
necessary or appropriate.
Reprinting personal information
Please note that any information you post
to a public bulletin board or chat room, is available to all
persons accessing that site.
Privacy related concerns
Should you have questions or concerns
relating to this Privacy Statement or compliance with it, please use the
following form to contact us:
Email:
Subject:
Comment:
QUOTES TO REMEMBER
Americans who value freedom had better be more concerned about the gun control crowd than the criminals. The criminals want your money. The Neo-Totalitarians want your freedom.
— Charlie Reese
COPYRIGHT POLICY:
The posting of copyrighted articles and other content, in whole or in part, is not allowed here.
We have made an effort to educate our users about this policy and we are extremely serious about this.
Users who are caught violating this rule will be warned and/or banned.
If you are the owner of content that you believe has been posted on this site without your permission, please contact our webmaster by following this link.
Please include with your message: (1) the particulars of the infringement, including a description of the content, (2) a link to that content here and (3) information concerning where the content in question was originally posted/published. We will address your complaint as quickly as possible. Thank you.
NOTICE:  The information contained in this site is not to be considered
as legal advice. In no way are Keep And Bear Arms .com or any of its agents responsible
for the actions of our members or site visitors. Also, because this web site is a Free
Speech Zone, opinions, ideas, beliefs, suggestions, practices and concepts throughout
this site may or may not represent those of Keep And Bear Arms .com. All rights reserved.
Articles that are original to this site may be redistributed provided they are left
intact and a link to http://www.KeepAndBearArms.com
is given. Click here for Contact Information for
representatives of KeepAndBearArms.com.
Thawte.com is the leading provider of
Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) and digital certificate solutions used by enterprises,
Web sites, and consumers to conduct secure communications and transactions over the
Internet and private networks.
KeepAndBearArms.com, Inc. © 1999-2020, All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
